{"data":[{"question":"Cotton used to rank first between Alabama's crops, but it represents only a fraction of the agricultural production now.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Cotton","b":"rank","c":"between","d":"represents","answer":"3","explain":" - Between-> among","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Salmon lay their eggs and die in freshwater, although they live in salt water when most of their adult lives.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"lay","b":"although","c":"when","d":"adult lives","answer":"3","explain":" - When-> where","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"To building their nests, tailor - birds use their bills as needles.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"building","b":"nests","c":"their","d":"as","answer":"1","explain":" - Building-> to build","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Fountain pens first became commercial available about a hundred years ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first","b":"commercial","c":"about","d":"ago","answer":"2","explain":" - Commercial-> commercially","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"With its strong claws and its many protruding tooth a gopher is an excellent digger.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"With","b":"strong claws","c":"protruding tooth","d":"is","answer":"3","explain":" - Protruding tooth-> protruding teeth","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Drug addiction has resulted of many destroyed careers, and expulsions from school or college.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"of","c":"destroyed","d":"expulsions","answer":"2","explain":" - Of->in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Because of the Lewis and Clark Expedition, the United States begin to realize the true value of the Louisiana territory.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because","b":"begin","c":"the true value","d":"territory","answer":"2","explain":" - Begin-> began","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Americans annually import more than 3 billion worthy of Italian clothing, jewelry, and shoes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Americans","b":"more","c":"worthy","d":"clothing","answer":"3","explain":" - Worthy-> worth ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"Akuce Ganuktibm, she spent her life working with the health and welfare of the families of workers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"she","b":"her life","c":"welfare","d":"the","answer":"1","explain":" - She-> spend","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"},{"question":"There are many different ways of comparing the economy of one nation with those of another.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"There are","b":"of comparing","c":"those","d":"another","answer":"3","explain":" -Those-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"38","type":"1"}]}